[
    {
        "front": "sino",
        "back": "but"
    },
    {
        "front": "asimismo",
        "back": "in addition"
    },
    {
        "front": "ademas",
        "back": "besides"
    },
    {
        "front": "recorrer",
        "back": "travel/tour"
    },
    {
        "front": "demas",
        "back": "the rest"
    },
    {
        "front": "vacilantes",
        "back": "hesitant"
    },
    {
        "front": "por los demas",
        "back": "for others"
    },
    {
        "front": "tras",
        "back": "after"
    },
    {
        "front": "por lo demas",
        "back": "otherwise"
    },
    {
        "front": "cifra",
        "back": "figure"
    },
    {
        "front": "pesima",
        "back": "lousy"
    },
    {
        "front": "ejemplar",
        "back": "copy"
    },
    {
        "front": "anaquel",
        "back": "shelf"
    },
    {
        "front": "acudir",
        "back": "go"
    },
    {
        "front": "acostar",
        "back": "lie down"
    },
    {
        "front": "agotar",
        "back": "exhaust"
    },
    {
        "front": "magna",
        "back": "great"
    },
    {
        "front": "reseña",
        "back": "review"
    },
    {
        "front": "tirada",
        "back": "circulation"
    },
    {
        "front": "nutrido",
        "back": "nourished"
    },
    {
        "front": "unanimente",
        "back": "unanimously"
    },
    {
        "front": "juicio",
        "back": "opinion"
    },
    {
        "front": "buhardilla",
        "back": "attic"
    },
    {
        "front": "retornar",
        "back": "return"
    },
    {
        "front": "parva",
        "back": "dull"
    },
    {
        "front": "asco",
        "back": "disgust"
    },
    {
        "front": "rigida",
        "back": "stiff"
    },
    {
        "front": "parvos",
        "back": "few"
    },
    {
        "front": "voluntad",
        "back": "will"
    },
    {
        "front": "esclusa",
        "back": "lock"
    },
    {
        "front": "cuza",
        "back": "whole"
    },
    {
        "front": "delante",
        "back": "in front of"
    },
    {
        "front": "burda",
        "back": "unrefined"
    },
    {
        "front": "remarcar",
        "back": "remark"
    },
    {
        "front": "envejecer",
        "back": "grow old"
    },
    {
        "front": "silla de ruedas",
        "back": "wheelchair"
    },
    {
        "front": "escapar",
        "back": "become scarce"
    },
    {
        "front": "quebrar",
        "back": "break"
    },
    {
        "front": "mohoso",
        "back": "moldy"
    },
    {
        "front": "siendo",
        "back": "being"
    },
    {
        "front": "infame",
        "back": "infamous"
    },
    {
        "front": "aparatoso",
        "back": "spectacular"
    },
    {
        "front": "alcanzar",
        "back": "scope"
    },
    {
        "front": "mazmorra",
        "back": "dungeon"
    },
    {
        "front": "brillo",
        "back": "glow"
    },
    {
        "front": "codificar",
        "back": "convert"
    },
    {
        "front": "desidia",
        "back": "neglect"
    },
    {
        "front": "suele",
        "back": "usually"
    },
    {
        "front": "codicia",
        "back": "greed"
    },
    {
        "front": "deslumbramiento",
        "back": "glare"
    },
    {
        "front": "tales",
        "back": "such"
    },
    {
        "front": "ensayo",
        "back": "essay"
    },
    {
        "front": "peregrinaje",
        "back": "pilgrimage"
    },
    {
        "front": "capricho",
        "back": "whim"
    },
    {
        "front": "sumar",
        "back": "add"
    },
    {
        "front": "extrañar",
        "back": "entertain exile"
    },
    {
        "front": "temer",
        "back": "fear"
    },
    {
        "front": "rol",
        "back": "role"
    },
    {
        "front": "hallar",
        "back": "find"
    },
    {
        "front": "que",
        "back": "whatever"
    },
    {
        "front": "espanto",
        "back": "terror"
    },
    {
        "front": "piadoso",
        "back": "pious"
    },
    {
        "front": "placentura",
        "back": "pleasant"
    },
        {
            "front": "Fructuosa",
            "back": "fruitful"
        },
        {
            "front": "Telón",
            "back": "curtain"
        },
        {
            "front": "Arrolladora",
            "back": "overwhelming"
        },
        {
            "front": "Huellas",
            "back": "footprints"
        },
        {
            "front": "Trasunto",
            "back": "transcript"
        },
        {
            "front": "Fondo",
            "back": "background"
        },
        {
            "front": "Entretejer",
            "back": "to interweave"
        },
        {
            "front": "Legado",
            "back": "legacy"
        },
        {
            "front": "Inmarcesible",
            "back": "unfading"
        },
        {
            "front": "Concitar",
            "back": "Agitate"
        },
        {
            "front": "Exabrupto",
            "back": "outburst"
        },
        {
            "front": "Lo que sea",
            "back": "whatever"
        },
        {
            "front": "Abstuvar",
            "back": "to abstain"
        },
        {
            "front": "Secundar",
            "back": "to second"
        },
        {
            "front": "Catedratica",
            "back": "professor"
        },
        {
            "front": "Furgoneta",
            "back": "van"
        },
        {
            "front": "Lapidaria",
            "back": "lapidary- related to stone cutting, engraving, etc"
        },
        {
            "front": "Adlatere",
            "back": "associate"
        },
        {
            "front": "Contraponer",
            "back": "Oppose"
        },
        {
            "front": "Colmo",
            "back": "height"
        },
        {
            "front": "Lomo",
            "back": "spine"
        },
        {
            "front": "Estrecha",
            "back": "narrow"
        },
        {
            "front": "Llovizna",
            "back": "drizzle"
        },
        {
            "front": "Velada",
            "back": "evening"
        }
]